<article class="static">

  <div class="measure">
    <h1>Contact</h1>

    <p>Before making contact, please be mindful about the following:</p>

    <p>Data in The Danish National Research Database is based on a harvest of metadata records directly from the suppliers.</p>

    <p>Therefore:</p>

    <ul>
      <li>
        The database does not hold actual material. No assistance with regards to ordering material is offered. In order to get a hold of any publications found in this database, follow backlinks to the originating CRIS — it may offer access options.  Otherwise, a library (public or research) or the publisher may help. 
      </li>
      <li>
        If you have corrections to any of the publication data found in this database, contact the data provider which provided the metadata.  Any data changes should be done in the CRIS systems of the data providers.  See <a href="/about/data-formats">Data Formats</a> for more.
      </li>
    </ul>

    <p><strong>For electronic contact:</strong></p>

    <!-- TODO: is this correct HML5? -->
    <p class="adr">
      Email: <a href="mailto:info@forskningsdatabasen.dk">info@forskningsdatabasen.dk</a>
    </p>

    <p><strong>For formal contact:</strong></p>

    <p class="adr vcard">
      <span class="organization-unit">
        <strong class="name">The Danish National Research Database</strong><br />
        Project Management
      </span>
      <br />
      <span class="organization-name">c/o DTU Library</span>
      <br />
      <span class="street-address">
        Anker Engelunds Vej 1,<br />
        Bygn. 101 D, Postboks 777,
      </span>
      <br />
      <span class="postal-code">DK-2800</span>
      <span class="locality">Kgs. Lyngby</span><br />
    </p>

<!-- TODO: validate

    <p class="vcard">
      <a class="fn org url" href="http://www.w3.org/Consortium/contact-keio" title="Contact Information for W3C/Keio">
        <span class="organization-name">W3C</span>/<span class="organization-unit">Keio</span>
      </a>
      <br>

      <span class="adr">
        <a class="extended-address" href="http://www.keio.ac.jp/english/about_keio/campus_info/sfc1.html">
          Keio  University Shonan Fujisawa Campus
        </a>
        <br>

        <span class="street-address">5322 Endo</span>,
        <span class="locality">Fujisawa city</span>,<br>
        <span class="region">Kanagawa prefecture</span>
        <span class="postal-code">252-8520</span>
        <b class="country">Japan</b><br>
        <span class="tel">Telephone:
          <span class="value">+81-466-49-1170</span>
        </span><br>
        <span class="tel">
          <span class="type">Fax</span>:
          <span class="value">+81-466-49-1171</span>
        </span>
      </span>
    </p>
  -->

</div>
</article>

